Guide to the AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council records, 1935-1978; 1962-1976; 0450-003; 62.97 cubic feet 63 boxes
  - ORGANIZATIONAL RECORDS, SERIES I
    - Legislation, Subseries E
      - Energy
        - Northwest Regional Power Bill, S. 3418, 1978 (Box-folder 6/27)
        - Utility Rates, HB 435, 1975 (Box-folder 6/28)
      - Environment - Conservation of Resources
        - Proposal to use Hood Canal as a Rearing Pond for Stocking Puget Sound, Initiative 52, 1976 (Box-folder 6/29)
      - Environmental Legislation
        - Alpine Lakes Region of Washington, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 6/30)
        - Beverage Container Control - miscellaneous legislation, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 6/31)
        - Environmental Protection Act (Draft), HB 782, 1971 (Box-folder 6/32)
      - Foreign Trade and Investment Act, D. 2592, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 6/33)
      - Health and Medical Programs
        - Health Insurance Benefits Act of 1961, HR 4222 (Box-folder 6/34)
        - Health Premium Payments for Striking and Locked-out Employees, HB 239, 1975 (Box-folder 6/35)
        - Health and Welfare Pension Plans, 1969 (Box-folder 6/36)
        - Patient's Bill of Rights, HB 1278, 1976 (Box-folder 6/37)
        - Miscellaneous Health Legislation, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 6/38)
      - Industrial Insurance
        - An Act Relating to Industrial Insurance, S. 529, 1971 (Box-folder 7/1)
        - An Act Relating to Industrial Insurance, HB 735, 1971 (Box-folder 7/2-7/3)
        - Board of Industrial Insurance Appeals Proposal, 1974 (Box-folder 7/4)
        - Industrial Insurance
          - HB 50, 1958, Undated (Box-folder 7/5)
          - HB 277, 1972 (Box-folder 7/6)
          - HB 321, 1975 (Box-folder 7/7)
          - HB 450, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 7/8)
        - National Workers Compensation Standards Act of 1973, S. 2008
          - General Correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 7/9)
          - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box-folder 7/10)
          - Resume of Insurance Laws, 1969 (Box-folder 7/11)
          - Workman's Compensation; H 1436, 1971 (Box-folder 7/12)
          - Miscellaneous Industrial Insurance Legislation, 1976 (Box-folder 7/13)
      - Labor Law
        - Age Discrimination in Employment Act of 1967, P.L. 90-202, 81 Statute 602, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 7/14)
        - Bacon-Davis Act of 1931, 1955-1979 (Box-folder 7/15-7/16)
        - Collective Bargaining, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 7/17)
        - Emergency Public Protection Act, SB 3526, 1970 (Box-folder 7/18)
        - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1970
          - General Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box-folder 7/19-7/22)
          - Circulars to Affiliates, 1960-1977 (Box-folder 7/23)
          - Legislation, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 7/24)
          - Statements and Testimony, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7/25-7/26)
          - Reports, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 7/27)
          - Statistics, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 7/28)
          - Ephemera, 1959-1973 (Box-folder 7/29)
          - Miscellaneous, 1965-1977, Undated (Box-folder 7/30)
        - Industrial Welfare Orders
          - General Correspondence, 1961-1976 (Box-folder 7/31-7/34)
          - Legislation, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 7/35)
          - Reports, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 8/1)
          - Statements and Testimony, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 8/2-8/3)
          - Newsletters, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 8/4)
          - Notes, Undated (Box-folder 8/5)
          - Ephemera, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 8/6)
          - Miscellaneous, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 8/7)
          - Subject Series: Industrial Welfare Committee Proceedings and Actions, 1962-1976 (Box-folder 8/8-8/10)
        - Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1959 (Box-folder 8/11)
        - Laws Affecting Private Household Workers, 1975 (Box-folder 8/12)
        - Minimum Wage Bills, SB 425, HB 522, HB 643, 1961 (Box-folder 8/13)
        - Moving Picture Projectionist Legislation, SB 29, 1969 (Box-folder 8/14)
        - New California Labor Law, 1975 (Box-folder 8/15)
        - Printing Trades Legislation Program, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 8/16)
        - Proposed Washington State Labor Relations Act, 1967-1969; 2 folders (Box-folder 8/17-8/18)
        - Proposed Washington State Labor Relations Bills, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 8/19-8/20)
        - Situs Picketing Bill, S. 1479, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 8/21)
        - Social Workers Licensing Law, 1969 (Box-folder 8/22)
        - Taft-Hartley Act, 1947-1969 (Box-folder 8/23)
        - Miscellaneous Labor Laws, National, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 8/24)
      - Log Exports
        - Ban on Log Exports, Initiative 32, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 8/25-8/26)
      - Maritime Legislation
        - Federal Maritime Act of 1966, HR 15567 (Box-folder 8/27)
        - Merchant Marine Act of 1920 (Jones Act) as Amended, S. 2454, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 8/28)
        - Merchant Marine Act of 1936 (as Amended) S. 1773 (1963), S. 2419 (1967), 1963-1967 (Box-folder 8/29)
        - "Midbody Bill," HR 163, 1969 (Box-folder 8/30)
      - Monopoly
        - Hart Anti-Trust Bill S. 3832, 1972 (Box-folder 8/31)
      - Optional Insurance
        - Optional Insurance, HB 399, 1953 (Box-folder 8/32)
      - Public Assistance
        - Better Jobs and Income Act, HR 9030, 1968-1979 (Box-folder 8/33-8/35)
        - Employment Relations Act (Proposed), 1977 (Box-folder 8/36)
        - Pension Reform, Initiative 333, 1976 (Box-folder 8/37)
      - Safety-Occupational and Industrial
        - Coal Mine Health and Safety Act, P.L. 91-173, 1969 (Box-folder 9/1)
        - Inspection of Towboats on Inland Waterways, HR 156, 1967 (Box-folder 9/2)
        - Occupational Safety and Health Act of 1970, HR 16785
          - General Correspondence, 1964-1972 (Box-folder 9/3-9/5)
          - Reports, Statements and Testimony, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 9/6)
          - Miscellaneous, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 9/7)
        - State Safety Legislation, SB 169, 1972 (Box-folder 9/8)
        - Washington Industrial Safety and Health Act (WISHA) of 1973
          - General Correspondence, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 9/9)
          - Legislation, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 9/10)
          - Miscellaneous, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Social Security
        - Amendments to the Social Security Act, P.L. 86-778, 1960 (Box-folder 9/12)
        - Social Security, HR 12080, 1967 (Box-folder 9/13)
      - Taxes
        - Amending the Constitution to Repeal Exemptions, HJR#1, 1971 (Box-folder 9/14)
        - Corporate Income Tax, Initiative #284, 1974 (Box-folder 9/15)
        - Fannin Amendment, 1969 (Box-folder 9/16)
        - Miscellaneous Property Tax Measures, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 9/17)
        - Multistate Tax Compact, SB 247, 1967 (Box-folder 9/18)
        - Property Taxes - Proposed 25% Assessment, SB 623, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 9/19)
        - State Tax Limitation, 20 mills, Initiative 44, 1971 (Box-folder 9/20)
        - Surtax, HR 12290, 1969 (Box-folder 9/21)
        - Tax Proposals - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box-folder 9/22)
        - Tax Reform
          - HJR 37, SSB 2247, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 9/23-9/25)
          - HJR 42, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 9/26)
          - HJR 82, SJR 119, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 9/27)
        - Tax Reform Act of 1969, HR 13270 (Box-folder 9/28)
        - Taxation Based on Actual Use, HJR #1, 1968 (Box-folder 9/29)
        - Taxes, 1969 Legislative Session (Box-folder 9/30)
        - The Revenue Act of 1971 (Box-folder 9/31)
        - Twelve-Percent Corporate Income Tax, Initiative 314
          - General Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 9/32)
          - Reports, Speeches and Writings, 1975 (Box-folder 9/33)
          - Ephemera, 1975 (Box-folder 9/34)
          - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box-folder 9/35)
        - Variable Gas Tax Bill, SB 2159, 1975 (Box-folder 9/36)
      - Unemployment Compensation
        - Unemployment Compensation, HR 8282, 1965 (Box-folder 9/37-9/38)
        - Unemployment Compensation, HB 563, 1977 (Box-folder 9/39)
        - Unemployment Compensation, miscellaneous House Bills, 1973 (Box-folder 10/1)
        - Unemployment Compensation, miscellaneous Senate Bills, 1973 (Box-folder 10/2)
        - Unemployment Compensation, miscellaneous Legislation
          - General Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 10/3-10/5)
          - Legislation and Reports, 1969 (Box-folder 10/6)
          - Miscellaneous, 1962-1975 (Box-folder 10/7-10/15)
      - Washington Housing Corporation Act, 1971 (Box-folder 10/16)
      - Legislation - Miscellaneous
        - Organization - Legislative Rosters, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 10/17)
        - General Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 10/18-10/23)
        - Interoffice Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 10/24)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 10/25)
        - Circulars, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 10/26)
        - Legislation, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 10/27-10/29)
        - Reports, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 10/30-10/32)
        - Statements and Testimony, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 10/33)
        - Conferences and Conventions, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 10/34)
        - News Releases, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 10/35)
        - Roll Calls, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 11/1-11/5)
        - Vote Abstracts, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 11/6)
        - Clippings, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 11/7-11/9)
        - Ephemera, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 11/10-11/11)
    - Conferences and Conventions, Subseries F
      - Washington State Labor Council Annual Conventions, 1st-15th, 1958-1972; 105 folders (Box-folder 11/12-13/31)
      - Washington State Labor Council 1st Biennial Convention, 1974 (Box-folder 13/32-13/39)
      - American Association of State Compensation Insurance Funds, 22nd Annual Convention, Miami, Florida, November 7-9, 1963 (Box-folder 14/1)
      - AFL-CIO Housing Conference, San Francisco, 1974 (Box-folder 14/2-14/3)
      - AFL-CIO Housing Conference, New Orleans, 1976 (Box-folder 14/4)
      - Bargaining Relationships and Practices Conference, Tacoma, October 1967 (Box-folder 14/5)
      - Cardiac-In-Industry Conference, Longview, Washington, March 11, 1964 (Box-folder 14/6-14/7)
      - Critical Issues in State Government, George Meany Center for Labor Studies, Silver Springs, Maryland, 1976 (Box-folder 14/8-14/9)
      - Governors Industrial Safety Conference, 14th, 15th, 19th, 1963, 1964, 1968 (Box-folder 14/10-14/12)
      - Governor's Outdoor Recreation Conference, Olympia, December 17, 1962 (Box-folder 14/13)
      - Idaho State AFL-CIO Convention, 6th, Sun Valley, 1964 (Box-folder 14/14)
      - Industrial Tour, 6th, 1964 (Box-folder 14/15-14/16)
      - Industrial Union Section, Seventh Annual Meeting, Port Angeles, Washington, August 9, 1964 (Box-folder 14/17)
      - Institute on Current Labor Law, Seattle, 1960 (Box-folder 14/18)
      - Labor Institute for the United Steelworkers of America, 12th, Pullman, Washington, 1962 (Box-folder 14/19)
      - Labor Law Reform Workshop, Seattle, 1967 (Box-folder 14/20)
      - League of Women Voters Conference on Military Spending and National Security, 3rd, Seattle, 1971 (Box-folder 14/21)
      - National Conference of Health, Welfare and Pension Plans, 9th Annual, Miami, November 10-14, 1963 (Box-folder 14/22)
      - Northwest Community Service Conference, Portland, October 15, 1962 (Box-folder 14/23)
      - Northwest Council for Economic Education-Economic Education Workshop, Seattle, June 30, 1961 (Box-folder 14/24)
      - Northwest Regional Forum on Social Security, Seattle, 1977 (Box-folder 14/25)
      - Northwest Regional Institute on Rehabilitation and Labor Health Services, University of Washington, 1961 (Box-folder 14/26-14/27)
      - Nurse Shortage Conference, Seattle, September 27, 1963 (Box-folder 15/1)
      - Oregon AFL-CIO Convention, 7th, Salem, August 29-31, 1962 (Box-folder 15/2)
      - Oregon-Washington AFL-CIO Summer School, Portland, Oregon, August 4-9, 1963 (Box-folder 15/3-15/4)
      - Oregon-Washington Leadership Institute, Portland, Oregon, August 4-9, 1963 (Box-folder 15/5)
      - "Quest for Quality" Conference, Seattle, University of Washington Campus, November 19-20, 1962 (Box-folder 15/6)
      - A State Legislative Challenge: Workmen's Compensation, Center for Legislative Improvement, New Orleans, 1978 (Box-folder 15/7-15/8)
      - Unemployment Compensation Workshop, 1975 (Box-folder 15/9)
      - United States Department of Labor Golden Anniversary Dinner, Seattle, 1963 (Box-folder 15/10)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers, 24th, Tacoma, 1964 (Box-folder 15/11)
      - WSLC Legislative Conferences, Seattle, 1958, 1960 (Box-folder 15/12-15/13)
      - WSLC John H. Stender Appreciation Dinner, Seattle, 1973 (Box-folder 15/14-15/15)
      - Western Governors Conference, Scottsdale, Arizona, April 21-24, 1963 (Box-folder 15/16)
      - White House Conference on "The Industrial World Ahead - A Look at Business in 1990," Washington D.C., 1971 (Box-folder 15/17)
      - Workshop - Labor and Mental Health, Olympia
        - General Correspondence, 1965 (Box-folder 15/18)
        - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box-folder 15/19)
    - Subject Files, Subseries G
      - Aeronautics and Aerospace, Sub-Subseries 1
        - Air Travel and Air Fare, 1970 (Box-folder 15/20)
        - United States Space and SST Program, Undated (Box-folder 15/21)
      - Agricultural Workers and Farmers, Sub-Subseries 2
        - Agricultural Workers and Farmers
          - General Correspondence, 1953-1958 (Box-folder 15/22)
          - Miscellaneous, 1964-1977 (Box-folder 15/23)
        - Agricultural Labor Camps
          - General Correspondence, 1968-1976 (Box-folder 15/24)
          - Miscellaneous, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 15/25)
        - Farm Workers Legal Fee Case, 1976 (Box-folder 15/26)
        - "Migrant Ministry", 1963-1971 (Box-folder 15/27)
        - National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor
          - General Correspondence, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 15/28)
          - Reports, 1967 (Box-folder 15/29)
        - National Campaign for Agricultural Democracy, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 15/30)
        - National Farmers Organization, 1973 (Box-folder 15/31)
        - National Farmers Union, 1954-1971 (Box-folder 15/32)
        - National Sharecroppers Fund, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 15/33)
        - Workmen's Compensation for Farm Workers
          - General Correspondence, Undated (Box-folder 15/34)
          - Clippings, Undated (Box-folder 15/35)
          - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box-folder 15/36)
      - Alaska, Sub-Subseries 3
        - Alaska Federation of Labor
          - Alaska Disaster Fund, 1964 (Box-folder 16/1)
        - Alaska Salmon Industry
          - General Correspondence, 1939-1964 (Box-folder 16/2-16/3)
          - Newsletters, 1957-1962 (Box-folder 16/4)
          - Miscellaneous, 1952-1965 (Box-folder 16/5)
      - Apprenticeship and Training, Sub-Subseries 4
        - Manpower Development and Training, 1976 (Box-folder 16/6)
        - Oregon, Apprenticeship and Training Act, 1967 (Box-folder 16/7)
        - Seattle Opportunities Industrialization Center, Operation Outreach, Undated (Box-folder 16/8)
        - Washington Labor and Industries Department, Apprenticeship Council
          - General Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 16/10)
          - Minutes and Agenda, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 16/11)
          - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box-folder 16/12)
      - Banks and Banking, Sub-Subseries 5
        - Renton Community Bank, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 16/13)
        - Washington Legislature, Banking, Insurance and Utility Regulation Committee (Interim), 1971 (Box-folder 16/14)
      - Business and Commerce, Sub-Subseries 6
        - Unethical Business Practices, 1960; Sub-Subseries 7 (Box-folder 16/15)
      - Civil Defense, Sub-Subseries 8
        - Labor Civil Defense Orientation, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 16/16)
        - Seattle-King County Civil Defense, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 16/17)
      - Civil Rights and Equal Opportunities, Sub-Subseries 9
        - Civil Rights and Equal Opportunities
          - General Correspondence, 1965-1977 (Box-folder 16/18)
          - Miscellaneous, 1968-1977 (Box-folder 16/19)
        - Action Committee for Minority Employment, 1972 (Box-folder 16/20)
        - American Civil Liberties Union, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 16/21)
        - Equal Employment Opportunities, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 16/22)
        - Equal Rights Amendment, 1974 (Box-folder 16/23)
        - Jettie J. Murray vs. Ironworkers #86, Undated (Box-folder 16/24)
        - Labor and Employment of Minorities, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 16/25)
        - National Association of Intergroup Relations Officials (N.A.I.R.O.), 1966 (Box-folder 16/26)
        - National Urban League, 1959 (Box-folder 16/27)
        - Seattle Opportunities Industrialization Center
          - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 16/28)
          - Reports, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 16/29-16/31)
          - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box-folder 16/32)
        - Seattle Post Intelligencer Series, "Equal Rights", July-August 1972 (Box-folder 16/33)
        - Washington Discrimination, State Board Against
          - General Correspondence, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 16/34)
          - Speeches and Reports, 1966, Undated (Box-folder 16/35)
          - Clippings, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 16/36)
          - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box-folder 16/37)
        - Washington Governor, Youth Involvement, Commission for, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 16/38)
        - Women and Industrial Orders, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 16/39)
      - Consumer Protection, Sub-Subseries 10
        - AFL-CIO Correspondence and Statements, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 16/40)
        - Christian Science Monitor Consumer Series, 1970 (Box-folder 16/41)
        - Consumer Education, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 16/42)
        - National Commission on Consumer Finance, 1970 (Box-folder 16/43)
        - Professional and Occupational Licensing, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 16/44)
        - Retail Installment Credit, 1970 (Box-folder 16/45)
      - Credit and Interest Rates, Sub-Subseries 11
        - Credit and Interest Rates, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 17/1)
        - Credit Bureaus - Credit Unions, 1970, 1975 (Box-folder 17/2)
        - Installment Loan Act, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 17/3)
      - Crime and Delinquency, Sub-Subseries 12
        - Committee for the Children's Institution (Referendum 13), 1963-1964 (Box-folder 17/4)
        - Correctional Education, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 17/5)
        - Employment of Offenders, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 17/6)
        - King County, Justice Court, Probation Program, 1968 (Box-folder 17/7)
        - Lie Detectors, 1965 (Box-folder 17/8)
        - National Council on Crime and Delinquency, Washington Council, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 17/9)
        - Organizing Correctional Institutions, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 17/10)
        - Prison Reform ("Attica Resolution"), 1971 (Box-folder 17/11)
        - Probation and Parole, 1960 (Box-folder 17/12)
      - Dams and Waterways, Sub-Subseries 13
        - Columbia River Navigation Project, 1970 (Box-folder 17/13)
        - Inland Empire Waterways Association, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 17/14)
        - Lower Snake River Dams Project - Lower Monumental, Little Goose and Lower Granite, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 17/15)
        - Middle Snake River Hydroelectric Project
          - General Correspondence, 1962-1975 (Box-folder 17/16)
          - Legislation, 1968, 1975 (Box-folder 17/17)
          - Resolutions, 1955, 1961 (Box-folder 17/18)
          - Statements, 1968, 1973 (Box-folder 17/19)
          - Miscellaneous, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 17/20)
        - National Rivers and Harbors Congress, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 17/21)
        - Pacific Northwest River Basins Commission, 1972 (Box-folder 17/22)
        - Ross Dam
          - General Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 17/23)
          - Statements, 1972 (Box-folder 17/24)
          - Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 17/25)
      - Drugs and Pharmacy, Sub-Subseries 14
        - Drug Abuse, 1971 (Box-folder 17/26)
        - Generic Names and Prices
          - General Correspondence, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 17/27)
          - Clippings, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 17/28)
          - Miscellaneous, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 17/29)
        - Prophylactic Act Revision, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 17/30)
        - Washington Pharmacy Board
          - General Correspondence, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 17/31)
          - Legislation, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 17/32)
          - Miscellaneous, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 17/33)
      - Economic Policies and Programs, Sub-Subseries 15
        - Economic Policies and Programs
          - General Correspondence, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 17/34-17/35)
          - Speeches and Writings, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 17/36)
          - Statements, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 17/37-17/79)
          - Ephemera, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 17/40)
          - Interaction, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 17/41)
          - Jobs Now - Washington Future Programs, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 17/42)
      - Education, Sub-Subseries 16
        - Education
          - General Correspondence, 1966-1978 (Box-folder 18/1-18/2)
          - Speeches and Writings, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 18/3)
          - Ephemera, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 18/4)
        - Congressional Scholars Program, 1974 (Box-folder 18/5)
        - Elementary and Secondary Education Act, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 18/6)
        - Financial Aid to Students, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 18/7)
        - High Schools, 1970 (Box-folder 18/8)
        - Labor Studies in Public Schools, 1963-1972 (Box-folder 18/9)
        - National Institute of Labor Education, 1967 (Box-folder 18/10)
        - Promotion of Labor Studies, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 18/11)
        - School Funding, 1975 (Box-folder 18/12)
        - Washington State Labor Council - Seattle Community
          - College Sponsorship of TV High School (Box-folder 18/12)
          - General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 18/13)
          - Questionnaires, 1969 (Box-folder 18/14)
          - Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 18/15)
      - Education and Vocational Rehabilitation, Sub-Subseries 17
        - National Institutes on Rehabilitation and Health Services, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 18/16)
      - Educational and Cultural Exchange, Sub-Subseries 18
        - Japanese Consulate
          - General Correspondence, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 18/17)
          - Miscellaneous, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 18/18)
      - Elections, Sub-Subseries 19
        - Elections
          - General Correspondence, 1958-1976 (Box-folder 18/19-18/29)
          - General Correspondence with National Committe of Political Education (COPE), 1970 (Box-folder 18/30)
          - Financial Records -- Candidate Contributions, 1962-1972 (Box-folder 18/31-18/35)
          - Vote Talleys, 1932-1976; 6 folders (Box-folder 18/36-19/1-19/2)
          - Campaign Materials, 1960-1976 (Box-folder 19/3-19/5)
          - Questionnaires - Candidates, 1968-1976 (Box-folder 19/6-19/10)
          - Lists - Candidates, 1960-1976 (Box-folder 19/11-19/17)
          - Ephemera, 1958-1976 (Box-folder 19/18-19/27)
        - Committee on Political Education (COPE) King County, 1962 (Box-folder 19/28)
        - Evans, Daniel J., 1968 (Box-folder 20/1)
        - Gubernatorial Candidates, C-4 Reports, 1976 (Box-folder 20/2)
        - Hermann Campaign Deficit Dinner, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 20/3)
        - Humphrey for President, 1968 (Box-folder 20/4)
        - Junior Citizens for Kennedy, 1968 (Box-folder 20/5)
        - League of Women Voters, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 20/6)
        - May, Catherine, 1968 (Box-folder 20/7)
        - O'Connell, John, 1968 (Box-folder 20/8)
        - Open Primary Elections, 1974 (Box-folder 20/9)
        - Platforms, 1972 (Box-folder 20/10-2/14)
        - Presidential Candidates' Positions, 1972 (Box-folder 20/15)
        - Senate Democratic Caucus Candidates and Issues Meeting, 1974 (Box-folder 20/16)
        - Wallace Candidacy, 1968 (Box-folder 20/17)